easypostjob4u.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy

## Who we are

> Our website address is: https://www.easypostjob4u.com.

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

#### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

Company Policy – We believe people are our strength and they are fundamental to our company’s continued existence and growth.

Company’s Security Policy – Our privacy is our business and your privacy is also very important to us. When you provide us with information we expect it to be for us only. Your privacy is our responsibility and our privacy safeguard also depends on your action and business plan. It is for your information that privacy of each others will generate better and reliable business. We maintain strict controls over information you provide to us. Company policies are subjected to change but not the right to privacy. We will share information as per our contract and will not include people / company from outside our system.

Registration – We provide you with classified information regarding our company and we give you access to our system with Id & Password for check your work, report & payment status. You also provide us with your name, postal addresses, Email ID and Telephone numbers when registering. This information is used strictly for our office use only.

Security of your Information – Any information you provide to Universal Info Service over this website is maintained and accessible only by Universal Info Service and its authorized partners. Universal Info Service uses this information to transfer information related to service updates, special offers and notifications..

### Contact forms

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
